ooh
哦
no I don't feel confident in it at all
不，我对此根本不自信
is difficult for even basic to get like jobs
即使基本的工作也很难像工作一样
I say research writing where doing what
我说研究写作在哪里做什么
I didn't find it that useful as like a creative major
我没有像创意专业那样有用
as well as like an international student
以及像国际学生一样
yeah for people who actually take advantage of them
是的，对于真正利用他们的人
not me
不是我
I am Christine
我是克里斯汀
I'm currently working for
我目前为
a career strategist company called Elite
一家名为Elite的职业战略家公司
Share or Ling Xuan
分享或ling Xuan
so first I want to ask you
所以我首先要问你
have you been doing any internships
你有没有实习
I have not been doing any internships
我没有做任何实习
I've applied to a couple and I've gotten like rejected
我已经申请了一对夫妇，我被拒绝了
I haven't done any internships
我没有做任何实习
or like proper internships
或喜欢适当的实习
because I've always missed the date by like that much
因为我一直想念那样的日期
and it's driving me a little bit insane
这让我有点疯狂
but hopefully I can get that work experience
但希望我能获得那种工作经验
not yet unfortunately
不幸的是
I have been on the search for like an internship but
我一直在寻找实习，但是
I have not been able to get one
我已经无法得到一个
so yeah but here's to hoping for next summer
是的，但这是希望明年夏天
what do you think of the current job market right now
您现在如何看待当前的就业市场
like do you feel confident in it
就像你对此充满信心
ooh
哦
no I don't feel confident in it at all
不，我对此根本不自信
I am slightly dreading going
我有点害怕
if I go to Santa Barbara having to
如果我去圣塔芭芭拉必须
reapply for jobs
重新申请工作
I never felt confident entering the job market
我从未有信心进入就业市场
to begin with
首先
just because
只是因为
I don't feel like I have a lot of experience
我觉得我没有很多经验
I don't expect to get a full time job straight away
我不希望能马上完成全职工作
like I had watched my friend
就像我看过我的朋友
as she graduated last year and had to apply for jobs
当她去年毕业，不得不申请工作
and it took her a while before she could get anything
她花了一段时间才能得到任何东西
so I was like looking at jobs and I was like ooh
所以我就像看工作一样，就像哦
this does not look good
这看起来不好
like there were I was applying
就像我在申请
there was when I was applying to jobs
在我申请工作的时候
before I got my current job
在我当前工作之前
it was like a constant ghosting
就像一个不断的鬼魂
like
喜欢
I would apply to a job I did submit like my resume
我会申请我像简历一样提交的工作
submit a cover letter and then no I'd hear
提交求职信，然后没有我听到
I wouldn't hear back from anyone
我不会听到任何人的回音
the job market right now
现在的就业市场
and the way that like
和喜欢的方式
I guess HR and human resources deals with it
我想人力资源和人力资源正在处理它
feels very disheartening
感到非常沮丧
especially because they don't
特别是因为他们没有
outright tell you no
彻底告诉你不
they just like ghost and that is almost worse
他们就像鬼一样，这几乎更糟
what has been challenging for you while job hunting
在狩猎工作时对您充满挑战的是什么
I think the scope of it
我认为它的范围
I'm sure this is true of a lot of
我敢肯定这是如此
graduates but especially for me
毕业生，尤其对我来说
if I say oh I want to go into writing
如果我说哦，我想写作
well where doing what
好吧，在哪里做
I say research writing where doing what
我说研究写作在哪里做什么
you know would I want to work full time for a company
你知道我想为公司全职工作
is there specific company I want to work for like
我想喜欢的特定公司吗
do I want to focus on where in the work chain
我想专注于工作链中的位置吗
am I involved in
我参与吗
so just the massive scope
所以只是巨大的范围
of opportunity is very alarming
机会非常令人震惊
yeah that seems really difficult
是的，这似乎真的很困难
to just narrow down what exactly you want to do
只是缩小您想做什么
have you used career services on campus
您是否在校园使用了职业服务
at all and have you found them to be helpful
根本没有发现它们有帮助
I have actually not used career services
我实际上没有使用职业服务
I
我
did think about getting in touch with them in the fall
确实考虑过在秋天与他们联系
but I just
但是我只是
didn't end up ever making an appointment with them
最终从来没有和他们约会
I did go to the career fair but
我确实参加了职业博览会
I didn't find it that useful
我没发现有用
as like a creative major
就像一个创意专业
as well as like an international student
以及像国际学生一样
you can't like they won't guide you around by the hand
你不喜欢他们不会指导你
there's like a good number of career fairs I've seen
我见过的很多职业博览会
and I'm like
我就像
and the department sends the emails with like
部门以喜欢的方式发送电子邮件
research opportunities and internships
研究机会和实习
and those kinds of things
还有那种事情
and like of course there's a like
就像当然有类似
department advisor you always you can always go to
部门顾问，您总是可以去
so I feel like they have quite
所以我觉得他们有
they have good services
他们有好的服务
for people who want to like reach out to them
对于想与他们联系的人
I see but for people who want to reach out
我明白了，但对于那些想伸出援手的人
yeah for people who actually take advantage of them
是的，对于真正利用他们的人
not me
不是我
it's most helpful
这是最有帮助的
when you already know what questions to ask
当您已经知道要问什么问题时
I know you know
我知道你知道
all advisors are there
所有顾问都在那里
oftentimes just to help you identify
通常只是为了帮助您识别
what questions you need to ask
您需要问什么问题
before you even know which ones you need
在您甚至知道您需要哪些之前
is there any advice that you give a high schooler
有什么建议您给高中生
who's kind of currently uncertain about their future
谁目前不确定他们的未来
don't do exactly what I did but at the same time
不要完全做我所做的，而是同时做的
really exploring your options I think will help you
真正探索您的选择，我认为会帮助您
figure out what you want to do
弄清楚你想做什么
the easiest thing is to just put yourself out there
最简单的是把自己放在那里
it's great
这很棒
if you can find something that you love to do
如果您可以找到自己喜欢做的​​事情
but just like
但是就像
to get the experience on some level
在某种程度上获得体验
is probably the best
可能是最好的
if you're less of a like
如果你不喜欢
I mean right now
我的意思是现在
especially the job market being what is
特别是就业市场是什么
at least here in the US
至少在美国
is difficult for even basic to get like jobs
即使基本的工作也很难像工作一样
like what is it entry level was even pretty difficult
就像入门级甚至很困难
I would have to say that like
我不得不说喜欢
just putting yourself out there is normally
只是把自己放在那里通常
is like a pretty great idea
就像一个很棒的主意
what you're actually gonna get
你实际上会得到什么
while when you put yourself out there is debatable
当你把自己放在那里的时候
but it's a journey for all of us
但这是我们所有人的旅程
and it's not going to happen
这不会发生
if you don't take that first step
如果您不采取第一步